const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '681 − 374 =', answer: '307', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '742 − 415 =', answer: '327', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '764 − 257 =', answer: '507', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '381 − 118 =', answer: '263', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '653 − 237 =', answer: '416', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '632 − 218 =', answer: '414', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '843 − 127 =', answer: '716', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '521 − 304 =', answer: '217', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '763 − 547 =', answer: '216', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '874 − 258 =', answer: '616', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];